Hudson River Sloop Clearwater, Inc. Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 1. Environmental Action, 1; 37.5 Linear Feet Boxes: 1 - 41 Folders: 1 - 1126
  - Subseries 1.24: Wastewater Treatment, 1.24; Boxes: 31 - 32 Folders: 893 - 933
    - General Accounting Office Water Pollution Reports (Folder 913, Box 31)
    - Handbook for Monitoring Industrial Wastewater (Folder 914, Box 31)
    - Incorporation of Sublethal Effects and Indirect Mortality in Modeling Population-Level Impacts of a Stress, with an Example Involving Power-Plant Entrainment and Striped Bass (Folder 915, Box 31)
    - Indian Point (Folder 916, Box 31)
    - Industrial Pretreatment Citizen Handbook (Folder 917, Box 31)
    - Mitigating Aquatic Impacts at Bowline Point, Indian Point Units 2 and 3 and Roseton Generating Stations (Folder 918, Box 31)
    - Mitigation of Impingement Impact at Hudson River Power Plants (Folder 919, Box 31)
    - Mohawk River Municipal WWTP Headworks Analysis (Folder 920, Box 31)
    - New York State Energy Plan Volumes I and II (Folder 921, Box 31)
    - New York State Energy Plan Volume III (Folder 922, Box 31)
    - New York State Water Pollution Control Revolving Loan Fund (Folder 923, Box 32)
    - New York’s Persistent Energy Crisis (Folder 924, Box 32)
    - Notes on Certain of the Testimonial Documents that Pertain to the Effects of Power Plants on Striped Bass in the Lower Hudson River and Estuary (Folder 925, Box 32)
    - Pace University School of Law Energy Project (Folder 926, Box 32)
    - Petition for Fair Competition in the Electric Industry (Folder 927, Box 32)
    - Pretreatment: Chesapeake Bay (Folder 928, Box 32)
    - Riverbalance: A Mass Balance Model for Assessing the Water Quality Impact of Chemical Discharges to Rivers (Folder 929, Box 32)
    - Save the Bay: Reducing Toxic Pollution in Narragansett Bay (Folder 930, Box 32)
    - Sludge Management Plan: New York City Industrial Pretreatment Program (Folder 931, Box 32)
    - Toxic Chemicals in Industrial Wastewater (Folder 932, Box 32)
    - Trust Us. Don’t Track Us: An Investigation of the Chemical Industry’s “Responsible Care” Program (Folder 933, Box 32)
  - Subseries 1.25: Croton Point, 1.25; Box: 32 Folders: 934 - 940
    Series contains documents concerning environment and landfill environment impacts at Croton Point.
    - 1981 Croton Point Landfill Investigation (Folder 934, Box 32)
    - Clippings (Folder 935, Box 32)
    - Croton Landfill (Folder 936, Box 32)
    - Croton Point Dredging Project Draft Environmental Impact Statement (Folder 937, Box 32)
    - Croton Watershed (Folder 938, Box 32)
    - Site Inspection Report for Croton Point Sanitary Landfill (Folder 939, Box 32)
    - Village of Croton-on-Hudson Water System (Folder 940, Box 32)
  - Subseries 1.26: Delaware/Lower Hudson region, 1.26; Box: 32 Folders: 941 - 947
    Series contains documents concerning water resources management strategy of Delaware/Lower Hudson Region
    - Comments on Delaware/Lower Hudson Region Water Resources Management Strategy (Folder 941, Box 32)
    - Correspondence (Folder 942, Box 32)
    - Delaware/Lower Hudson Region Counties (Folder 943, Box 32)
    - Delaware/Lower Hudson Region Water Resources Management Strategy (Folder 944, Box 32)
    - Draft Delaware/Lower Hudson Region Water Resources Management Strategy (Folder 945, Box 32)
    - Proceedings (Folder 946, Box 32)
    - Proposed Modifications to Delaware/Lower Hudson Region Water Resources Management Strategy (Folder 947, Box 32)
  - Subseries 1.27: Chelsea Pumping, 1.27; Boxes: 33 - 34 Folders: 948 - 974
    Series contains documents concerning Pumping Plant at Chelsea, New York
    - 1989 Emergency Use Authorization (Folder 948, Box 33)
    - Chelsea Emergency Water Supply Project Table of Contents (Folder 949, Box 33)
    - Chelsea Interim Briefs 1 (Folder 950, Box 33)
    - Chelsea Interim Briefs 2 (Folder 951, Box 33)
    - Chelsea Interim Briefs 3 (Folder 952, Box 33)
    - Chelsea Party Filings (Folder 953, Box 33)
    - Chelsea Pumping Plant Hearing 1989 (Folder 954, Box 33)
    - Clearwater Comments on Drought Operation of the Hudson River Pumping Plant at Chelsea, New York (Folder 955, Box 33)
    - Clippings (Folder 956, Box 33)
    - Comments on Draft Environmental Impact Statement (Folder 957, Box 33)
    - Comptroller’s Report (Folder 958, Box 33)
    - Drought Operation of the Hudson River Pumping Plant Located at Chelsea, Dutchess County, New York Draft Environmental Impact Statement (no folder) (Folder 959, Box 33)
    - General Background (Folder 960, Box 33)
    - Hudson River Fishermen’s Association Plaintiff (Folder 961, Box 33)
    - The Impending Pollution of New York City’s Water Supply (Folder 962, Box 33)
    - Mayor’s Intergovernmental Task Force on New York Water Supply Needs (Folder 963, Box 33)
    - Miscellaneous (Folder 964, Box 33)
    - New York City Municipal Water Finance Authority (Folder 965, Box 33)
    - New York City Proposed Revision to Permit Application (Folder 966, Box 33)
    - New York City Water Conservation Plan (Folder 967, Box 34)
    - News Releases (legal) (Folder 968, Box 34)
    - Newton Creek Consent Order (Folder 969, Box 34)
    - The Review Journal of the International Water Supply Association (Folder 970, Box 34)
    - Rules and Regulations Governing and Restricting the Use and Supply of Water (Folder 971, Box 34)
    - Salt Front Migration (Folder 972, Box 34)
    - Water Conservation (Folder 973, Box 34)
    - Water Conservation Manual for Development of a Water Conservation Plan (Folder 974, Box 34)
  - Subseries 1.28: Fish and Wildlife, 1.28; Boxes: 34 - 35 Folders: 975 - 1021
    Series contains documents concerning protection of fish and wildlife
    - 1991 Supplement to the Hudson River Striped Bass Stock Assessment (Folder 975, Box 34)
    - A.C. Dutton Lumber Corporation Effects on Wildlife (Folder 976, Box 34)
    - A Collection of Papers on Ecology of Hudson River Fishes (Folder 977, Box 34)
    - A Perspective of Past Estuarine Fisheries Research in the Hudson Estuary as a Guideline for Future Efforts to Promote, Protect and Enhance Fisheries Resources of that Ecosystem (Folder 978, Box 34)
    - A Study of Dioxin in Aquatic Animals and Sediments (Folder 979, Box 34)
    - Abundance and Stock Characteristics of the Atlantic Tomcod Spawning Population in the Hudson River, Winter 1990-91 (Folder 980, Box 34)
    - Abundance and Stock Characteristics of the Atlantic Tomcod Spawning Population in the Hudson River, Winter 1991-92 (Folder 981, Box 34)
    - An Analysis of Avian Breeding Habitats in Hudson River Tidal Marshes (Folder 982, Box 34)
    - Analysis of Fisheries Sampling Programs Conducted in the Hudson River with an Overview of the Biological Productivity of that Ecosystem (Folder 983, Box 34)
    - Avian Breeding Habits in Hudson River Tidal Marshes (Folder 984, Box 34)
    - Biology and Management of Shortnose and Atlantic Sturgeon of the Hudson River (Folder 985, Box 34)
    - Clippings (Folder 986, Box 34)
    - Correspondence (Folder 987, Box 34)
    - DEC Division of Fish and Wildlife Environmental Impact Statement on Fish Species Management Activities (Folder 988, Box 34)
    - The Dryland Fish Book (Folder 989, Box 34)
    - The Endangered Shortnose Sturgeon of the Hudson Estuary: Its Life History and Vulnerability to the Activities of Man (Folder 990, Box 34)
    - Fish Migratory Patterns (Folder 991, Box 35)
    - Habitat Sustainability Index Models and Instream Flow Sustainability Curves: Shortnose Sturgeon (Folder 992, Box 35)
    - Health Risks from Fish (Folder 993, Box 35)
    - Hudson River Estuary Fishery Management Program 1985 Annual Report (Folder 994, Box 35)
    - Hudson River Estuary Fishery Management Program Progress Report for 1982-1984 (Folder 995, Box 35)
    - Hudson River Fisheries Development Program (Folder 996, Box 35)
    - Hudson River Striped Bass Hatchery Evaluation/Monitoring Program (Folder 997, Box 35)
    - Impact of Drought on Fisheries (Folder 998, Box 35)
    - Marine Resource Management Needs (Folder 999, Box 35)
    - Miscellaneous (Folder 1000, Box 35)
    - Monitoring PCB in Hudson River Striped Bass 1978-1985 (Folder 1001, Box 35)
    - New York Fish and Game Journal (Folder 1002, Box 35)
    - New York Fisheries Program (Folder 1003, Box 35)
    - News Releases (Folder 1004, Box 35)
    - Performance Report for Biology and Management of Shortnose and Atlantic Sturgeons of the Hudson River 4/1/1976 - 3/31/1977 (Folder 1005, Box 35)
    - Performance Report for Biology and Management of Shortnose and Atlantic Sturgeons of the Hudson River 7/19/1977 - 3/31/1978 (Folder 1006, Box 35)
    - Population Dynamics of the Atlantic Tomcod in the Hudson River Estuary (Folder 1007, Box 35)
    - Protection of Shellfish Waters (Folder 1008, Box 35)
    - Recommendations for Adoption of Limited Entry Commercial Fishing Regulations in the Hudson River Estuary (Folder 1009, Box 35)
    - Sampling Ichthyoplankton (Folder 1010, Box 35)
    - Shad Bay of Fundy Project (Folder 1011, Box 35)
    - Striped Bass ’85 Ban (Folder 1012, Box 35)
    - Sturgeons of the Hudson River (Folder 1013, Box 35)
    - Synopsis of Biological Data on Shortnose Sturgeon (Folder 1014, Box 35)
    - Temporal and Spatial Aspects of PCB Contamination in Hudson River Striped Bass (Folder 1015, Box 35)
    - Testimony for the U.S. House of Representatives Subcommittee on Fisheries and Wildlife Conservation and the Environment (Folder 1016, Box 35)
    - Toxic Substances in Fish and Wildlife: 1979 and 1980 Annual Reports (Folder 1017, Box 35)
    - Toxic Substances in Fish and Wildlife: May 1 to November 1, 1981 (Folder 1018, Box 35)
    - Toxic Substances in Fish and Wildlife: November 1, 1981 to April 30, 1982 (Folder 1019, Box 35)
    - Trends in Levels of Several Known Chemical Contaminants in Fish from New York State Waters (Folder 1020, Box 35)
    - U.S.-Canadian Joint Effort Helps to Revitalize Great Lakes Fishery (Folder 1021, Box 35)
  - Subseries 1.29: Coastal Zone Management, 1.29; Box: 36 Folders: 1022 - 1037
    Series contains documents concerning the development and protection of New York’s coast
    - Action Alerts (Folder 1022, Box 36)
    - Articles on Use of Zoning to Protect Resources (Folder 1023, Box 36)
    - Funding: Coastal Management (Folder 1024, Box 36)
    - Funding: Private (Folder 1025, Box 36)
    - Funding: State (Folder 1026, Box 36)
    - General Zoning: Planning (Folder 1027, Box 36)
    - Jail Barge 1 (Folder 1028, Box 36)
    - Jail Barge 2 (Folder 1029, Box 36)
    - Jail Barge 3 (legal) (Folder 1030, Box 36)
    - New York State Coastal Coalition (Folder 1031, Box 36)
    - New York State Coastal Conference 1989 (Folder 1032, Box 36)
    - New York State Coastal Program (Folder 1033, Box 36)
    - New York State Coastal Zone Management Program Laws (Folder 1034, Box 36)
    - Now and for the Future: A Vision for New York’s Coast (Folder 1035, Box 36)
    - Task Force on Coastal Resources (Folder 1036, Box 36)
    - Village of Mamaroneck Underwater Lands Study (Folder 1037, Box 36)
  - Subseries 1.30: Public Access, 1.30; Boxes: 36 - 37 Folders: 1038 -1071
    Series contains documents concerning public access of New York’s land and water
    - A Vision for the Hudson River Waterfront Park (Folder 1038, Box 36)
    - Between the Railroad and the River: Public Access Issues and Opportunities (Folder 1039, Box 36)
    - Expanding Opportunities for Conservation and Recreation (Folder 1040, Box 36)
    - Habitat Bill (Folder 1041, Box 36)
    - Hudson-Mohawk Urban Cultural Management Plan Summary (Folder 1042, Box 36)
    - Hudson River Basin Project: Water Resources (Folder 1043, Box 36)
    - Hudson River Basin: Water and Related Land Resources Study (Folder 1044, Box 37)
    - The Journal of Land Trust Alliance Exchange (Folder 1045, Box 37)
    - Land Use/ Waterfront Articles Pre-‘92 (Folder 1046, Box 37)
    - Long Dock Recreational Use (Folder 1047, Box 37)
    - Marina Bill (Folder 1048, Box 37)
    - Marinas (Folder 1049, Box 37)
    - Marine Pump Out Stations (Folder 1050, Box 37)
    - Miscellaneous 1 (Folder 1051, Box 37)
    - Miscellaneous 2 (legal) (Folder 1052, Box 37)
    - National Public Trust Study: Filling of Shorelands (Folder 1053, Box 37)
    - Notes and Pamphlets (Folder 1054, Box 37)
    - Protecting Public Resources for the Needs of Today and Future Generations (Folder 1055, Box 37)
    - Public Access: General (Folder 1056, Box 37)
    - Public Lands Law and Regulations (Folder 1057, Box 37)
    - Public Trust Correspondence (Folder 1058, Box 37)
    - Public Trust Doctrine: Albany Law School (Folder 1059, Box 37)
    - The Public Trust Doctrine: The Ownership and Management of Lands, Water and Living Resources (Folder 1060, Box 37)
    - Public Trust Reports and Articles (Folder 1061, Box 37)
    - Reasons for and Effects of Inadequate Public Access (Folder 1062, Box 37)
    - Recommendations for Improving Public Recreational Access to the Hudson River (Folder 1063, Box 37)
    - Recreational Boating (Folder 1064, Box 37)
    - Recreational Boating Pollution (Folder 1065, Box 37)
    - Reports and Papers (Folder 1066, Box 37)
    - Riverside Park Fund (Folder 1067, Box 37)
    - Scope of the Public Trust Doctrine in New York State (Folder 1068, Box 37)
    - Sierra Club (Folder 1069, Box 37)
    - Underwater Land Bill (Folder 1070, Box 37)
    - The Use of the Public Trust Doctrine as a Management Tool for Public and Private Lands (Folder 1071, Box 37)
  - Subseries 1.31: Office of General Services, 1.31; Box: 38 Folders: 1072 - 1081
    Series contains documents released by Office of General Services
    - Accelerated Land Disposition Program (Folder 1072, Box 38)
    - Albany Yacht Club (Folder 1073, Box 38)
    - Dover Property (Folder 1074, Box 38)
    - Freedom of Information Law (Folder 1075, Box 38)
    - Freedom of Information Request (legal) (Folder 1076, Box 38)
    - Office of General Services Legislation (Folder 1077, Box 38)
    - Office of General Services Papers (Folder 1078, Box 38)
    - Real Property Planning and Policy review Committee Guidelines (Folder 1079, Box 38)
    - Red Hook (Folder 1080, Box 38)
    - Underwater Land: Hudson River Files (Folder 1081, Box 38)
  - Subseries 1.32: Critical Environmental Areas, 1.32; Boxes: 38 - 39 Folders: 1082 - 1094
    Series contains documents concerning critical environmental areas in various New York counties
    - Albany County CEA’s (Folder 1082, Box 38)
    - CEA’s in New York (Folder 1083, Box 38)
    - CEA Zoning (Folder 1084, Box 38)
    - Columbia County CEA’s (Folder 1085, Box 38)
    - Dutchess County CEA’s (Folder 1086, Box 38)
    - Greene County CEA’s (Folder 1087, Box 38)
    - Livingston Ridge on the Hudson Environmental Impact Statement (Folder 1088, Box 38)
    - Orange County CEA’s (Folder 1089, Box 38)
    - Putnam County CEA’s (Folder 1090, Box 38)
    - Rensselear County CEA’s (Folder 1091, Box 38)
    - Rockland County CEA’s (Folder 1092, Box 38)
    - South Troy Industrial Park Environmental Impact Statement (no folder) (Folder 1093, Box 39)
    - Ulster County CEA’s (Folder 1094, Box 39)
  - Subseries 1.33: Open spaces, 1.33; 1 Linear Foot Box: 39 Folders: 1095 - 1104
    Series contains pamphlets and documents concerning open space in New York State
    - Agricultural Land Acquisition (Folder 1095, Box 39)
    - Conservation Easements (Folder 1096, Box 39)
    - Conserving Open Space in New York State 1991 (Folder 1097, Box 39)
    - Conserving Open Space in New York State 1994 (Folder 1098, Box 39)
    - Conserving Open Space in New York State: A Summary of the Plan 1992 (Folder 1099, Box 39)
    - Greenway Clippings (Folder 1100, Box 39)
    - Greenway Pamphlets (Folder 1101, Box 39)
    - Hudson River Greenway (Folder 1102, Box 39)
    - Open Space Conservation Plan (Folder 1103, Box 39)
    - Regional Land Acquisition Advisory Committee (Folder 1104, Box 39)
  - Subseries 1.34: Adirondack Park, 1.34; 0.25 Linear Feet Box: 40 Folders: 1105 - 1108
    Series contains documents and maps of Adirondack Park
    - The Adirondack Park in the Twenty-First Century Volume I (Folder 1105, Box 40)
    - The Adirondack Park in the Twenty-First Century Volume II (Folder 1106, Box 40)
    - Adirondack Park Maps (Folder 1107, Box 40)
    - State of the Park (Folder 1108, Box 40)
  - Subseries 1.35: Southwood, 1.35; 0.25 Linear Feet Box: 40 Folders: 1109 - 1112
    Series contains documents concerning the protection of Southwood Estate
    - Maple Grove (Folder 1109, Box 40)
    - Southwood (Folder 1110, Box 40)
    - Southwood Articles and Maps (Folder 1111, Box 40)
    - St. Simeon (Folder 1112, Box 40)
  - Subseries 1.36: Hudson River Psychiatric Center, 1.36; 0.25 Linear Feet Box: 40 Folders: 1113 - 1116
    Series contains documents concerning the protection of the Hudson River Psychiatric Center
    - Correspondence (Folder 1113, Box 40)
    - Meetings and Notes (Folder 1114, Box 40)
    - OGS Hudson River Psychiatric Center Information (Folder 1115, Box 40)
    - Plan and Hearings (Folder 1116, Box 40)
  - Subseries 1.37: Scenic Areas, 1.37; 0.5 Linear Feet Boxes: 40 - 41 Folders: 1117 - 1126
    Series contains documents and maps of scenic areas of statewide significance
    - Glemnant Property (Folder 1117, Box 40)
    - Historic Sites (Folder 1118, Box 40)
    - Mid-Hudson Historic Shorelands (Folder 1119, Box 40)
    - Ossining Parcel (Folder 1120, Box 40)
    - River Edge Estates Environmental Impact Statement (Folder 1121, Box 40)
    - Rural Community Organizing (Folder 1122, Box 40)
    - Scenic Areas of Statewide Significance 1 (Folder 1123, Box 40)
    - Scenic Areas of Statewide Significance 2 (legal) (Folder 1124, Box 41)
    - Scenic Areas of Statewide Significance Maps (legal) (Folder 1125, Box 41)
    - Scenic Roads (legal) (Folder 1126, Box 41)
- 2. Publications, 2; 4.5 Linear Feet Boxes: 41 - 47 Folders: 1127 - 1341
  Series is divided into subseries containing printed materials, pamphlets, and reports collected by Clearwater
  - Subseries 2.1: MESA New York Bight Atlas Monographs, 2.1; 0.5 Linear Feet Box: 41 Folders: 1127 - 1152
    Series contains Monographs concerning aspects of New York environment
    - Aquaculture (Folder 1127, Box 41)
    - Artificial Fishing Reefs (Folder 1128, Box 41)
    - Beach Forms and Coastal Processes (Folder 1129, Box 41)
    - Benthic Fauna (Folder 1130, Box 41)
    - Chemical Properties (Folder 1131, Box 41)
    - Circulation (Folder 1132, Box 41)
    - Demographic Patterns (Folder 1133, Box 41)
    - Electricity Generation and Oil Refining (Folder 1134, Box 41)
    - Fisheries (Folder 1135, Box 41)
    - Gravity, Magnetics and Seismicity (Folder 1136, Box 41)
    - Hydrographic Properties (Folder 1137, Box 41)
    - Industrial Wastes (Folder 1138, Box 41)
    - Jurisdictional Zones and Governmental Responsibilities (Folder 1139, Box 41)
    - The Lower Bay Complex (Folder 1140, Box 41)
    - Marine and Coastal Birds (Folder 1141, Box 41)
    - Marine Climatology (Folder 1142, Box 41)
    - Plankton Production (Folder 1143, Box 41)
    - Plankton Systematics and Distribution (Folder 1144, Box 41)
    - Port Facilities and Commerce (Folder 1145, Box 41)
    - Recreation (Folder 1146, Box 41)
    - Sand and Gravel (Folder 1147, Box 41)
    - Storm Surge (Folder 1148, Box 41)
    - Surficial Sediments (Folder 1149, Box 41)
    - Tides (Folder 1150, Box 41)
    - Transportation (Folder 1151, Box 41)
    - Water Quality (Folder 1152, Box 41)
  - Subseries 2.2: Citizens Guides, 2.2; 0.25 Linear Feet Box: 42 Folders: 1153 - 1180
    Series contains manuals guiding the process of fighting for environmental rights
    - Citizens’ Environmental Coalition Fact Sheets 1-8 (Folder 1153, Box 42)
    - A Citizen’s Guide to Hazardous Waste Technologies and Resources (Folder 1154, Box 42)
    - A Citizen’s Guide to Promoting Toxic Waste Reduction (Folder 1155, Box 42)
    - A Citizen’s Guide to Protecting Seacoasts and the Great Lakes by Cleaning Up Polluted Runoff (Folder 1156, Box 42)
    - A Citizen’s Guide to Risk Screening (Folder 1157, Box 42)
    - A Citizen’s Guide to the Major Hazardous Waste Facilities Siting Act (Folder 1158, Box 42)
    - Citizen’s Guide to the New Federal Right-to-Know Law (Folder 1159, Box 42)
    - A Citizen’s Guide to Toxic Chemical Releases on Long Island (Folder 1160, Box 42)
    - A Citizen’s Toxic Waste Audit Manual (Folder 1161, Box 42)
    - DEC Guide to Public Hearings (Folder 1162, Box 42)
    - DEC Guides to SPDES (Folder 1163, Box 42)
    - Effective Citizen Participation in Public Hearings (Folder 1164, Box 42)
    - Elections - Grassroots Strategies for Change (Folder 1165, Box 42)
    - Glossary of Environmental Health Terms (Folder 1166, Box 42)
    - The Green Vote Handbook: Environmental&Electoral Politics (Folder 1167, Box 42)
    - A Guide to the Organization and Operation of Local Environmental Advisory Council (Folder 1168, Box 42)
    - A Guide to Reference Materials on Toxic Substances (Folder 1169, Box 42)
    - How to Challenge Your Local Electric Company (Folder 1170, Box 42)
    - Improving Dialogue with Communities (Folder 1171, Box 42)
    - An Introduction to Local Government in New York State (Folder 1172, Box 42)
    - An Introduction to Toxic Substances (Folder 1173, Box 42)
    - Local Government Handbook (Folder 1174, Box 42)
    - NRDC’s Guide to NPDES Permit (Folder 1175, Box 42)
    - Protecting Wetlands: What You Should Know (Folder 1176, Box 42)
    - A Public Citizen’s Action Manual (Folder 1177, Box 42)
    - A Review of Reynolds Metals Company SPDES Permit (Folder 1178, Box 42)
    - And Two if by Sea - Fighting the Attack on America’s Coasts (Folder 1179, Box 42)
    - Who to Contact for Help and Information about Environmental Health (Folder 1180, Box 42)
  - Subseries 2.3: Model Ordinance, 2.3; 0.25 Linear Feet Box: 42 Folders: 1181 - 1189
    Series contains publications concerning environmental concerns and how to fix them
    - Development Rights (Folder 1181, Box 42)
    - Flood Damage Prevention Law (Folder 1182, Box 42)
    - Incentive Zoning (Folder 1183, Box 42)
    - Lake Projection and Rehabilitation (Folder 1184, Box 42)
    - Planed Unit Development (PUD) Provisions (Folder 1185, Box 42)
    - Site Plan Review (Folder 1186, Box 42)
    - Stormwater and Erosion Control (Folder 1187, Box 42)
    - Stormwater Runoff (Folder 1188, Box 42)
    - Zoning Provisions (Folder 1189, Box 42)
  - Subseries 2.4: Department of Environmental Conservation (DEC) Regulations, 2.4; 0.75 Linear Feet Boxes: 42 - 43 Folders: 1190 - 1208
    Series contains pamphlets outlining DEC Regulations
    - Amendment to 6NYCRR Parts 940-941 (Folder 1190, Box 42)
    - Capital Region Water Resources Management Strategy (Folder 1191, Box 42)
    - Citizen Suit Policy (Folder 1192, Box 42)
    - Division of Water Annual Report: Fiscal Year 1990-1991 (Folder 1193, Box 42)
    - Hazardous Waste Reduction Law, 1990 (Folder 1194, Box 42)
    - Hazardous Waste Reduction Proposed, 1993 (Folder 1195, Box 42)
    - Hazardous Waste Reduction Proposed Regulations - Public Comment/Press (Folder 1196, Box 42)
    - Hazardous Waste Reduction Statutory Authority/TRI (Folder 1197, Box 42)
    - Multi-Media Pollution Prevention Advisory Group - Hazardous Waste Reduction (Folder 1198, Box 42)
    - Multi-Media Pollution Prevention (M2P2) Advisory Group (Folder 1199, Box 42)
    - Part 370 Series 360-14 (Folder 1200, Box 42)
    - Part 378 (Folder 1201, Box 42)
    - Part 378 Industry Business Council (Folder 1202, Box 42)
    - Part 378 Recent Stuff (Folder 1203, Box 42)
    - Part 624 Governing Permit Hearing Procedures (Folder 1204, Box 43)
    - Report of the Fixed Station Conventional Parameter Water Quality Surveillance Network 1985 (Folder 1205, Box 43)